<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-11T16:34:18-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Mary Mosman</title><subtitle>I’ve worked as a web developer at many companies throughout the Twin Cities, but teaching  programming &amp; web development to others has become what I'm passionate about. I’ve taught  people of all ages through formal college classes, corporate training, and less formal  gatherings &amp; meet-ups. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">New Job!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/08/02/new-job/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Job!" /><published>2021-08-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-08-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/08/02/new-job</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/08/02/new-job/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve had a nice month or so off, but today I got off to a great new start with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.techelevator.com/&quot;&gt;Tech Elevator&lt;/a&gt;. Looking forward to being part of their National Live Remote program. Woot for remote work &amp;amp; remote learning!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m pretty uncommitted to this blog at this point, so I’ll be taking a hiatus as I sort out my new job, a new relationship, and all sorts of future plans.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’ve had a nice month or so off, but today I got off to a great new start with Tech Elevator. Looking forward to being part of their National Live Remote program. Woot for remote work &amp;amp; remote learning!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fortunate Graduation!!!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/07/09/fortunate-graduation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fortunate Graduation!!!" /><published>2021-07-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-07-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/07/09/fortunate-graduation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/07/09/fortunate-graduation/">&lt;p&gt;My beloved Fortunate cohort graduated today! Woot!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We bravely gathered to celebrate graduation together had a little get together at the Crooked Pint downtown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Prime Fortunate Cohort&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/07/09/fortunate-graduation-5b89ba1a2c69b47ff9a529fea9bcdc340ad68312797f67dbd78f944980419f3b.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a little bitter-sweet as not only will I miss them dearly, but they will be my last Prime cohort. I’ve decided to leave as Prime heads back to campus this fall to continue working remotely.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My beloved Fortunate cohort graduated today! Woot!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">End of May?!!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/25/end-may/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="End of May?!!" /><published>2021-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/25/end-may</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/25/end-may/">&lt;p&gt;So it’s pretty much the end of May and I’m just kinda getting things together here to post again. I’m not gonna lie, for some reason this has been a tough month. The bathroom is still where it was at the end of April, and many little goals are still dangling out there just out of reach…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The combination of the rain and the heat has made for a rather depressing spring. It’s had the cats all zonked out for much of the last few weeks. This is what I see most days while I’m working… It’s not super inspirational - at least for anything other than napping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;All 3 cats zonked out while I work&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/05/25/lazy-cats-57001d9ecbe24818187fa97e0f688469ff306f1e507a040f40a2487f76c2557a.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did something happen? No and yes. No tragedy or life altering event, just a slow MN spring that turned into summer before I had a chance to enjoy it, and the continued uncertainty of the Covid-bound world. I do love my work from home job, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;BUT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; I really want to get back to meeting friends in the wild. To have breakfast - ah, the lemon ricotta pancakes - at Jensen’s again in the busy fullness of it all. It’s been much harder to keep trouping as we transition from winter pretty directly into summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got the 2nd vaccine shot over lunch today, and while my arm is super sore, I’m so glad to be on the road to feeling free again. I’ve already got plans 2 weeks out to reconnect with some long unseen friends. Woot!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cold spring got me looking at what it might take to pick up and move somewhere more pleasant year round, and that’s left me feeling a little up-rooted. I’ve toyed with the idea of everything from SC/NC to OR/WA to HI and have even considered remote work in Japan. I’m relatively loosly bound at this point, and would love to at least have less winter and more spring/fall. I’ve got a pull to try out Santa Fe, NM which could be interesting in its own ways, but my current fav is somewhere along the coast of Oregon. Those ocean views and the green… sigh…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did manage to snag a bunch of the lilacs last week, just before they (like my crabappple blossoms) faded much too fast. They (both the crabapple &amp;amp; lilac) only lingered for about a week before they were gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;a makeshift vase of lilacs&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/05/25/lilacs-aa10023149ed9fb0705193ac3de490b51475915f26dcfc2758621bde5537aa4e.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got a renewed goal to finish up the bathroom &amp;amp; kitchen trim work with an aim to sell the house before the end of summer. However, it is a little harder to think of leaving as I write this on the heavenly shaded deck. It was a bit muggy out in the wild earlier, but back here it’s beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Hanging out on the deck&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/05/25/hanging-on-deck-42f574670b332c8bb8fec4e3e7b82774583796d87e40b04366910343f29b96f9.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course there is Butter to keep my spirits up. Thank you to BTS and all the other artists who’ve been so vital to keeping my spirits up over the last more than a year now. Let’s not say how many times I’ve streamed this (and the other 2 versions) of this video since their releases…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WMweEpGlu_U&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So it’s pretty much the end of May and I’m just kinda getting things together here to post again. I’m not gonna lie, for some reason this has been a tough month. The bathroom is still where it was at the end of April, and many little goals are still dangling out there just out of reach…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spring!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/04/spring/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spring!" /><published>2021-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-05-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/04/spring</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/05/04/spring/">&lt;p&gt;It’s been a nice weekend, and I finally got myself outdoors to enjoy breakfast on the deck. The goal was to do some work on the blog, but I ended up not getting very far as it started raining on me before I finished my tea!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Enjoying breakfast on the deck&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/05/02/breakfast-on-deck-a663119b6c4e6dfac341c1c03792b809f51cd8814064b7b1468924c713cfdab8.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crabapple is in full bloom now, and dropping little pink petals all over my deck and table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;the crabapple in bloom&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/05/02/crabapple-blossoms-688bd9a753dbef4e43e0f15053ab79c8f62ecb58856d3a871777c45dcd9b2b1f.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m trying to be optimistic and keep thing running after finishing up all the bathroom work, but it’s hard to stay motivated! I also think I’m kinda stalling cuz I’m not quite really ready to sell the house now that the weather is nicer. But things are busier again at work too, and it is &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;hard&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to work through the week and then also continue that through the weekend too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It’s been a nice weekend, and I finally got myself outdoors to enjoy breakfast on the deck. The goal was to do some work on the blog, but I ended up not getting very far as it started raining on me before I finished my tea!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bathroom Almost Finished</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/30/bathroom-almost-finished/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bathroom Almost Finished" /><published>2021-04-30T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-04-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/30/bathroom-almost-finished</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/30/bathroom-almost-finished/">&lt;p&gt;So April is done, and the bathroom is mostly there. I managed to wrap-up the floor install, got the doors out &amp;amp; painted &amp;amp; back in. Then I decided to grout the floor too because I didn’t like the way it felt on my bare feet. It was a lot of work, but I’m really happy with the outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Bathroom is just missing the trim.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/30/bathroom-almost-done-7feee2ef34e59add1ced22c920cc65d5a760db5fc167507708389055b36d9642.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The vanity cabinet is looking top notch with the new floor.
&lt;img alt=&quot;white vanity with grey floor&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/30/finished-vanity-196b5c95f9ca4ab0a4a929acbcad65f5b93b0f5fb874732affd2a8c8d020682a.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grouting the peel &amp;amp; stick tiles made the look AND feel much better!
&lt;img alt=&quot;grey tiles filled w/ grout&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/30/grouted-tiles-f4c6f46886a6e84f5000eaf48f2abb573d4f837d6ed27c70f7ccd8555c8e3a3a.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part of this work was installing a bowed curtain rod for the shower. It has made a world of difference in my shower life. There is so much more space in there now &amp;amp; the curtain doesn’t touch me while showering! Woot!!! I am SO happy with this and it took maybe 20 minutes to take the old one out and put the new one in. 
&lt;img alt=&quot;shower curtain with curved rod&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/30/shower-curved-rod-b5db134d830ea10359cbc62a6d0cb8db97dc39f4a6d6c6224b40029166cf2fc9.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly the work is not &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;all done&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; yet as there’s no trim. I’ve been kinda in a bit of a procrastination slump and have been taking it a little easy over the last few cold &amp;amp; rainy weekends, but I’m determined to get this done over the next weekend or two.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So April is done, and the bathroom is mostly there. I managed to wrap-up the floor install, got the doors out &amp;amp; painted &amp;amp; back in. Then I decided to grout the floor too because I didn’t like the way it felt on my bare feet. It was a lot of work, but I’m really happy with the outcome.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">April…</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/05/april/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="April..." /><published>2021-04-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/05/april</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/homereno_2020_2021/covid-19/2021/04/05/april/">&lt;p&gt;Well, somehow April is here. The weather has been nicer, and while it’s rained a lot lately, it’s making it pretty and green faster. Woot! Even though the weather is warmer, I still haven’t been out much. I’ve been working on fixing up the bathroom so it isn’t the sore spot of my upstairs. It’s been an adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first task was to paint the vanity cabinet. The vanity was kinda beat up &amp;amp; somewhat puffy in places from the moisture. The floor was well… I feel like I remember floor like that from my wee years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took the doors off and pulled out the doors to spray paint them in the garage. 
&lt;img alt=&quot;The old dark wood cabinet without the doors &amp;amp; the old floor.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/old-cabinet-floor-86ef12948dbc4dfe8981d9e9ab7b51575509eb509b638640ef66ab145c34c3a7.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure if spray painting the cabinet itself in doors was the best idea. While it was quick, it made a HUGE mess everywhere to clean off the floor, vanity top, and just everywhere!!!
&lt;img alt=&quot;Painted the vanity white&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/painting-vanity-610d943d56509b28dedaa4aa1456c7e7bb4613816ecfb6e43d64dbb4cb639055.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also painted the pulls for the cabinet, so no more ugly brass.
&lt;img alt=&quot;Painting the cabinet pulls&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/cabinet-pulls-e1397866271bed5c0d03f126a64cd63d7a6ec1824328de6e00b90a3c7e1ccad7.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done!
&lt;img alt=&quot;Finished white vanity with pulls&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/vanity-finished-ef3b1139b0256414e558bb2adebe08bce7a691a61f3df6f40f0fd452da467be1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had some extra spray paint primer, so I thought I’d un-brown the door to the garage too. It was metal, so I didn’t think the interior paint would stick by itself. So, yet another mess was made…
&lt;img alt=&quot;Garage door primed, spotty, but not brown!&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/door-primed-514f9c2a050818346bf3de3d6c78db0094d374a87e8b2347f78bed7ce0f5b558.jpg&quot; /&gt; 
The primer coat was a splotchy mess, but it did make a fine base for the interior trim paint. With an additional coat of that, it came out beautifully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then the it was back to the bathroom for the walls &amp;amp; doors!
&lt;img alt=&quot;Lighter blue walls, and doors primed white.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/walls-primed-doors-e968bebc97c34a21d1641e229c9456449827c256df7c05d6c5431c7c5a6a4764.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After priming the doors, I had some help taking them down and carrying them to the basement to finish painting. They came out much better that way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally the floor had to go. First, I laid out the tiles to sort out colors and placement.
&lt;img alt=&quot;Tiles laid out on the floor&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/layout-tiles-be4da687ac0a7619f10dc0d261485e3ec8fa91b166b7e8cf03325388fa2a15dd.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it was time to peel and stick them down! I stopped at the tub &amp;amp; toilet, since the caulking and toilet had to come out to put the tile in. But the rest of it was done in about 2 hours, most of which was spent laying them out, cuz I’m indecisive about that stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Most of the floor in&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/floor-mostly-in-df3d79f516d007f64037fc71bd9efa2972450b4203ab0602831ffdfa710218c7.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the towel rack back up as well as the little glass shelf, it’s looking pretty good. As it all comes together, it’s like an entirely different place!
&lt;img alt=&quot;Sink area looking good&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/04/10/looking-good-73a179ad123d1170d30534f202cb381e816e88600aa95d938f4709447fc51f80.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Well, somehow April is here. The weather has been nicer, and while it’s rained a lot lately, it’s making it pretty and green faster. Woot! Even though the weather is warmer, I still haven’t been out much. I’ve been working on fixing up the bathroom so it isn’t the sore spot of my upstairs. It’s been an adventure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome Fortunate</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/04/05/welcome-fortunate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome Fortunate" /><published>2021-04-05T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/04/05/welcome-fortunate</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/04/05/welcome-fortunate/">&lt;p&gt;My 10th Prime cohort kicked off their full-time classroom work this week. Woot! I’m so excited! 10 is a big number!!! They feel extra special because we’re all decimal based and all - not to mention they are called Fortunate!!! There’s 14 of them too… that I also feel is &lt;em&gt;fortunate&lt;/em&gt;. ^.^ I’m going to have way too much fun with this crew.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">My 10th Prime cohort kicked off their full-time classroom work this week. Woot! I’m so excited! 10 is a big number!!! They feel extra special because we’re all decimal based and all - not to mention they are called Fortunate!!! There’s 14 of them too… that I also feel is fortunate. ^.^ I’m going to have way too much fun with this crew.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Spring in the air!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/03/05/march/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Spring in the air!" /><published>2021-03-05T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2021-03-05T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/03/05/march</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/03/05/march/">&lt;p&gt;The weather has been great the last week. Spring is in the air, at least for now. We all know it’ll likely disappear any moment, so we’re making the most of it while we can. It’ll almost be 60 on Sunday!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been nice to crack the windows open here over the last few days and get some fresh air, though it’s also likely run up my heating bill… It’s not &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; nice yet, but after a brutal below zero cold snap, we’re living it up while it’s in the 40-50s here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t really &lt;em&gt;gotten out&lt;/em&gt; or anything though. I’m still enjoying being a home-body, though it was nice to run the garbage out without putting on a coat. I was outside in a T-Shirt!!! That was way cool. I’m also aiming to do the first bit of 2021 grilling with Martin &amp;amp; Dave this weekend. I’m super excited for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the weather out of the way, I guess I can update a few other nifty things in my life. I’m feeling a bit better overall. It’s hard not to with more sunshine, daylight and fresh air. But not a lot has really changed. I did not get any work started on the house over my time off last week. However I did get to relax, play some games, listen to music, and just focus some things that I enjoy. That was really sweet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had some good kitty time on the couch that was much over due. Watched some movies and Netflix TV. I watched a little series called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netflix.com/title/80234304&quot;&gt;The Queen’s Gambit&lt;/a&gt;, got in a few more episodes of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netflix.com/title/80212301&quot;&gt;Terrace House&lt;/a&gt;, and watched the movie &lt;a href=&quot;netflix.com/title/81386963&quot;&gt;The Yin Yang Master&lt;/a&gt;. I really enjoyed The Queen’s Gambit, though I’m not sure it was enough to watch another season…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These aren’t couch pics, but I’m sure you’re feeling some kitty pic withdrawl…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Kyo in a box on the kitchen counter&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/kyo-box-e5f103e01d99456da7062d3e62b1bfe9fa8e9162df48abc7674387616bb31c70.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Fred sitting on my gift box with Abby in the background&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/fred-claiming-gift-bcac2efcd124527c96de0176e9c0ac0dda90e2e39151088f6cb0bdc0ff0322a3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got some sweet gifts from some of my students, which not only entertained the cats above, but me as well. I have been getting infinite joy from my new BTS socks that came with an awesome box of interesting snack foods. There were also some &lt;em&gt;fun&lt;/em&gt; sheet masks with designs on them. Super cute!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;BTS socks, Korean sheet masks &amp;amp; snacks&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/socks-snack-box-776ec72804fcb9a368b2aba5a9a0ed83a0fc6d2e75e78450680cdbbebb123e9c.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The socks are so awesome!!! I’ve been fan girling all week with a different pair each day. With 7 days in the week and 7 BTS members it’s perfect, and maybe it will get me to do the laundry regularly each week!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;BTS Jimin Socks&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/jimin-socks-2599d72f7ed4dd5250e2259ea1691959cd35364167c9b9eeb5797575b818328a.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img alt=&quot;BTS Suga Socks&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/suga-socks-0304fe01aa713f71103d53ce8e9eff8ffff267ec3fab68f0f1ecd9948dfbc8fe.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also spent some time last week converting a project for the kyudo folks from postgres to mysql. It was fun to get to do some coding again, and I haven’t used mysql in ages. I figured it would take a few hours total, but it took me that long just to get mysql installed and everything running. &amp;gt;.&amp;lt; D’oh!!! That’s what I get for not tripling my estimates!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had great support from the kitty boys as I worked though. How could you not want to keep going with scenes like this to support you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Fred and Kyo snuggling to share the pillow.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/snuggle-brothers-2d82fb95177045af25ce1d38fe93eb7a3bce3eeb88033cb9c4ec056dedb06917.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t look comfy, but they were like that for almost 40 minutes!!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also got to have a little musical fun last week with my new lyre. It’s pretty sweet!!! I’m actually pretty excited to learn to play a little. See if I can finally manage a stringed instrument. I can run up and down a C scale… That’s a good start, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Lyre&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/lyre-c14f60e69d63cc9a82e1278c1cb2070bb371ae768c5a271832942b7a4dfe3d60.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was too excited to try it out when it first came. It was cold from being outside, and I &lt;em&gt;knew&lt;/em&gt; I should wait for it to warm up to try it. But I was impatient and tried to tune it to play a little and broke a string. So the first thing I had to do was learn to replace one. Thank goodness it came with a replacement set!!! I’ve been much more careful with it since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christy and I were also chatting about cat toys the other day, and how sad it was that Kyo lost his little saftey beaver. It’s probably hidden somewhere, but it’s been missing for many weeks now. While talking with Christy, I decided to get online and order him another one. But then I saw amazon had sold out of them?! What would poor Kyo do without a safety beaver? Christy had me look on Chewy, where fortunately they still had some, so I got him 6 of them just to be safe! I also ended up adding in some squirrels and hedgehogs for fun, and to get the free shipping. Woot?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guess I shouldn’t be the only one with gifts, and they were so very happy with them when they arrived. (They are hollow and get filled with catnip.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Kyo with the squirrel&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/kyo-squirrel-f04f938764e472a133365480d42f998abf9f07cd218f2cb9fc1cffe5923017cd.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Kyo &amp;amp; Fred with the new toys&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/03/05/kyo-fred-toys-0c704f0dbe2484233f8961dd18bd05e3dee0b82989d2092dba21ee0e9ac0ffa7.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you ask, Abby was snoozing and couldn’t be bothered at first. She eventually made her way out, but really just wanted the catnip. A practical lady she is.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The weather has been great the last week. Spring is in the air, at least for now. We all know it’ll likely disappear any moment, so we’re making the most of it while we can. It’ll almost be 60 on Sunday!!!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">February Updates</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/02/22/february/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="February Updates" /><published>2021-02-22T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2021-02-22T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/02/22/february</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/covid-19/2021/02/22/february/">&lt;p&gt;I haven’t updated in a while, so I guess I should catch up on some things…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was called out that not only have I not updated the blog in a while, but I sounded a bit down and sad. Well, I was… I’m not sure that I saw it coming either. The last month or two now has been really rough. I’m not really at a point to process that all here on the blog, but it’s been busy and there’s been more than an average amount of stress of late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My cohort’s graduation, and the start of the next cohort here today, gives me a chance to kinda start over in the work world. It also gives a nice opportunity to take some time off. Woot! Looking forward to taking Wed-Fri off for a super long weekend. Hopefully that will give me some time to de-stress and process some of the things that I haven’t really had time to think through yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m now thinking pretty seriously about selling my house and at least for the short-term getting an apartment in or near downtown St. Paul again. I want to finish up a little more of the work we started on the house before I put it up for sale. Specifically I want to spiffy up the upstairs bathroom a bit, as it really stands out as crappy right now. Then, I need to finish the trim upstairs in the kitchen &amp;amp; bath and likely touch-up some of the paint in a few other places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basement needs a lot more love, so I really need to think about how much to do there. I need to do something for the flooring and the fireplace. There’s also a lot of trim work that needs done. I try not to think about the bathroom, but it’s the big sore spot right now as it’s totally torn out. Ugh…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;I WOK Asian Cuisine egg roll&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/02/22/egg-roll-ffa73be0fdd81cbccbf4e3001262d5199a063d2eb64a06487a1089abfec5bbb3.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, the thought is that I’ll get started on that over the upcoming time off. We’ll see I guess. In the mean time, I’m enjoying some awesome egg rolls from I WOK in Burnsville via Door Dash. Woot! Sometimes it’s the little things in life that matter, and these egg rolls rock. They’re also &lt;em&gt;HUGE&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I haven’t updated in a while, so I guess I should catch up on some things…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Vatti Graduation!!!</title><link href="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/02/19/vatti-graduation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vatti Graduation!!!" /><published>2021-02-19T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2021-02-19T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/02/19/vatti-graduation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://mbmosman.github.io/prime/covid-19/2021/02/19/vatti-graduation/">&lt;p&gt;Woot! My Vatti cohort graduated today! Wacka, wacka!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the first cohort to graduate where I just haven’t been able to see any of them in person &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;ever!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (Too cold to do an outdoor park certificate hand-off this time!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Prime Vatti Cohort&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/02/19/vatti-graduation-69dd6aa0293fa1d2b907222a9e4b661210102bd95d4c5e3aae546dfd8ad75028.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a little weird to think we’ve never met in person, but at the same time, it doesn’t feel at all like these are people I don’t know. We’ve had a great time together and have gotten to know each other so well despite being entirely remote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got my stickers updated with the Vatti Pacman! Wacka, wacka!
&lt;img alt=&quot;Prime Stickers w/ Vatti Pacman&quot; src=&quot;/assets/2021/02/19/sticker-update-b683049f399b5013e8dd89a5124a2e7487e2beb92fe593c05cac0f702078d5d8.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to miss having y’all in class, but can’t wait for that first happy hour!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Woot! My Vatti cohort graduated today! Wacka, wacka!</summary></entry></feed>